freegamescasual.com 2019-05-16

# Privacy Policy - Free Games Casual

A. INTRODUCTION

This privacy statement was last updated on October 20, 2010. Games Banner Network, Inc., a Virginia corporation, its affiliates and subsidiaries (collectively, "GBN") has created this privacy statement in order to disclose our information gathering and dissemination practices for our Internet websites (collectively, the "Website"). While GBN's Website is deemed to be a U.S. website, GBN abides by the safe harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union. Upon reading this privacy statement, you will know: 

  1. What personally identifiable information of yours or third party personally identifiable information is collected from you through the Website.
  2. The organization collecting the information.
  3. How the information is used.
  4. With whom the information may be shared.
  5. What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information.
  6. Information relating to the use of this Website by children, and how parents can access their children's information.
  7. The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under GBN's control.
  8. How you can access and correct any inaccuracies in the information collected about you.
Any questions, concerns or complaints regarding this statement should be directed to GBN by emailing [privacy@gamesbannernetwork.com](mailto:privacy@gamesbannernetwork.com) or writing to us at the following address: Games Banner Network, Inc 901 N. Pitt Street Suite 325 Alexandria, VA 22314 

Word from the Company

GBN has a strong commitment to providing superior service to all of our customers and visitors of this Website and particularly respecting your concerns about privacy. We understand that you may have questions about how this Website collects and uses information and we have prepared this statement to inform you of the privacy principles that govern the Website (the "Privacy Policy"). We will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information or a list of our customers to third parties. However, as described in more detail in Part C below, there are limited circumstances in which some of your information will be shared with third parties, under strict restrictions, so it is important for you to review this Privacy Policy. 

This Privacy Policy contains numerous general and technical details about the steps we take to respect your privacy concerns. 

Changes in Privacy Policy 

GBN wants you to be always aware of what personal information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we disclose it. All personal information, as further described in Part B, that we collect and maintain will be subject to the version of the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of such collection. GBN reserves the right to change the Privacy Policy from time to time at its sole discretion, and will prominently post any material changes on the home page of the Website. You will be given the opportunity to opt-out. If as the result of such changes, you want to alter the ways in which GBN is allowed to use your personal information, you can do so by correcting your information on your account (profile) in our Website or writing to us at the aforementioned email address. You will be deemed to have been made aware of, and will be subject to, the changes to the Privacy Policy by your continued use of the Website after such notice has been posted for thirty (30) days. 

Third Party Websites

GBN does not control the information collection and distribution policies on Internet domains other than those Internet domains that are under the control of GBN itself. When you are on the GBN Website, you may be directed to other sites that are beyond our control. These other sites may independently collect data, solicit personal information, or send their own cookies to you. GBN is not responsible for any use of the information including click-stream data created when using such third party sites. 

Legal Issues 

Website may be subject to the laws of various jurisdictions, including the laws of the United States of America, European Union and Russian Federation and other jurisdictions because the access to this Website may use Internet traffic of different jurisdictions, including the aforementioned. GBN will disclose personally identifiable information without your permission when required by law, or in good faith belief that such action is necessary to investigate or protect against harmful activities to GBN guests, visitors, associates, or property (including this Website), or to others. As mentioned above, laws related to personal identifiable information vary by country. 

GBN may be required by law enforcement or judicial authorities to provide personally identifiable information to appropriate governmental authorities. If requested by law enforcement or judicial authorities, we will provide this information upon receipt of the appropriate documentation. GBN may also provide information to law enforcement to protect its property and the health and safety of individuals as permitted by statute. 

B. COLLECTED INFORMATION 

Browsing 

This Website does not collect personally identifiable information from your computer when you browse the Website and request pages from our servers. This means that, unless you voluntarily and knowingly provide us with personally identifiable information, we will not know your name, your email address, or any other personally identifiable information. When you request a page from our Website, our servers may log the information provided in the HTTP request header, JavaScript or similar technical tools, including the IP number, the time of the request, the URL of your request, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, click-stream data and other information. We collect such information in order to make our Website function correctly and provide you the functionality that you see on this Website, as our servers use this information to deliver to you the pages on this Website. We also use this information to better understand how visitors use our Website and how we can better tune our Website, its contents and functionality to meet your needs. Without expressly informing you in each particular circumstance, we do not match such information with any of your personal information.

Information We Collect 

As a visitor to this Website, you can engage in many activities without providing any personal information as described above in Section Browsing. In connection with other activities, such as subscribing to the services offered on the Website, subscribing to periodic newsletters sent by GBN, downloading trial versions of software, communications with other users, taking part in user ratings or utilizing online software applications GBN may ask you to voluntarily supply us with certain information about yourself by filling out and submitting an online form. It is completely optional for you to engage in these activities. If you elect to engage in these activities, however, GBN may ask that you provide us personal information, defined as any information that identifies or can be used to identify, contact, or locate the person to whom such information pertains, including your first and last name, country, sex, date of birth, email address and other personal information. 

You never have to answer any questions, and you can decline this exchange of information at any time. However, if you should choose to withhold requested information, we may not be able to provide you with some of the services dependent upon the collection of this information. Depending upon the activity, some of the information that we ask you to provide is identified as mandatory and some as voluntary. If you do not provide the mandatory data with respect to a particular activity, you will not be able to engage in that activity. 

GBN will only share your information with outside parties in ways that are described in this privacy statement or if we are required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law, cooperate with law enforcement agencies, or comply with a legal process served on our Website. 

When you place an order for software or services online, you may be re-directed to a third-party Website. Any third-party company administers its own Privacy Policy that is not under the control of GBN. Prior to placing an online order, please review the Privacy Policy on that Website. 

You are provided an opportunity on the GBN Website to subscribe to a periodic newsletter. This newsletter is a marketing tool that allows GBN to inform you of new Products and Services, as well as other news relevant to the company. The subscription service requires you to provide your first and last name, country, date of birth, sex, as well as your email address. 

While the subscription list is maintained by a trusted third party affiliate, the list remains the sole exclusive property of GBN. Your name, date of birth, photographs if any and email address is not shared with any third party and will not be used to send you unsolicited communications. You can change your subscription preferences, including cancellation of your subscription by editing your account (profile) in the Website. 

When you submit personal information to GBN through this Website, you understand and agree that this information may be transferred across national boundaries and may be stored and processed in any of the countries in which GBN and its affiliates and subsidiaries maintain offices. You also acknowledge that in certain countries or with respect to certain activities, the collection, transferring, storage, and processing of your information may be undertaken by trusted vendors, partners of GBN. Such vendors, partners are bound by contract not to use your personal information for their own purposes or provide it to any third parties. 

GBN may establish relationships with various service providers whose services may become available to you from this Website or from other websites that are linked to this Website. Typically, these providers would offer services that GBN customers might find useful, such as those that can be used in conjunction with GBN services and products. In order to use those services, you may be required to provide personal information to the providers. Unless expressly provided to the contrary, personal information that you provide while you are visiting a provider's website will be subject to the privacy policy posted on such site, and personal information that you provide while on this Website will be subject to this Privacy Policy. You should be aware that our agreements with these service providers may provide that they will share with GBN personal information collected from you. In such instances, GBN may use this information in a manner consistent with this Privacy Policy. 

Information Relating to Children 

We recognize that children under the age of 13 may access this Website and subscribe to the newsletter, communicate with other users, take part in user ratings, utilize online software applications or download trial versions of software programs. The collection of information is covered above and shall comply with the United States Federal Trade CommissionвЂ™s ChildrenвЂ™s Online Privacy Protection Act (вЂњCOPPAвЂќ). Parents are required to participate and control their childrenвЂ™s online activities. 

When the child registries at the Website, he/she has to provide his/her age. Therefore if a child indicates that he/she is under 13, it will be required to add the email address of the Parents or Legal Guardians. GBN will notify them about their child registration on the Website.

Parents and Legal Guardians may request from us to review, delete or stop the collection of the personally identifiable information of their child. You may do so in one of two ways. If you know the user name and password or email address, follow the instructions below regarding Choices Available to You or you may contact us by letter, or email using the address information provided above in this statement. 

Securing the Transmission and Storage of Information 

GBN operates secure data networks protected by industry standard firewall and password protection systems. Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary, and only authorized individuals have access to the information provided by our users. Even your registration account password is encrypted before it is sent to our computers. 

GBN takes steps to ensure that your information is treated securely and in accordance with our Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you use these services at your own risk. 

We treat the information you provide to us as confidential information; it is, accordingly, subject to our company's security procedures and corporate policies regarding protection and use of confidential information. After personally identifiable information reaches GBN it is stored on a server with physical and electronic security features as customary in the industry, including utilization of login/password procedures and electronic firewalls designed to block unauthorized access from outside of GBN. Because laws applicable to personal information vary by country, our offices or other business operations may put in place additional measures that vary depending on the applicable legal requirements. Information collected on the sites covered by this Privacy Policy is processed and stored in the United States and also in other countries where GBN and its service providers conduct business. All GBN employees are aware of our privacy and security policies. Your information is only accessible to those employees who need it in order to perform their jobs. 

C. USE AND DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION 

How your personal information is used 

GBN collects your information in order to record and support your participation in the activities you select. We will use your email address to send an activation code to your account (profile) in the Website, notices about new messages, friends, congratulations with birthday and, if necessary, might use the other information to contact you for help to process the service you have selected. If you subscribe to a service, for example, the information is used to register your rights, if any, to technical support or other benefits that may be made available to registered users. Your personal information is also used to keep you informed about product upgrades, patches, special offers, and other products and services of GBN and selected third parties if you have so opted to receive such communications. 

GBN may collect information about the use of the Website, such as the types of services used, general age related, geographical, sexual structure of the traffic, and how many users we receive daily. This information is collected in aggregate form, without identifying any user individually. GBN may use this aggregate, non-identifying statistical data for statistical analysis, marketing, or similar promotional purposes. 

GBN recognizes and appreciates the importance of responsible use of information collected on this Website. Without your consent, GBN will not communicate any information to you regarding newsletters and special offers available from GBN, although we may find it necessary to communicate with you regarding your use of the services on this Website. Except in the particular circumstances described in this Privacy Policy, GBN will also not provide your name to other companies or organizations without your consent. 

Disclosure of Information to Third Parties 

GBN does use the services of third parties, such as email service providers, content providers, purchase and order processing merchants and marketing companies that act as independent contractors on behalf of GBN (the вЂњPartnersвЂќ). These parties are contractually prohibited from using personally identifiable information for any purpose other than for the purpose GBN specifies. We do provide non-personally identifiable information to certain Partners for their use on an aggregated basis for the purpose of performing their contractual obligations to us. We prohibit the sale or transfer of personal information to entities outside of GBN for their use without your approval. 

GBN may disclose your personally identifiable information if we believe in good faith that we are required to do so in order to comply with applicable law, a subpoena, or other legal process. GBN may also disclose personally identifiable information when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our Terms of Use, this Privacy Policy or to protect the safety of our users and the public or under confidentiality and licensing agreements with certain third parties which assist us in developing, operating and maintaining the Website and its content. 

In the event that all or substantially all of GBN's stock and/or assets are transferred or sold to another entity, GBN may transfer personally identifiable information to the acquiring entity. If, as a result of such a business transition, your personally identifiable information will be used in a materially different manner, you will be given choice consistent with our policy regarding notification of changes. 

Choices available to you 

You can always choose whether or not to disclose personally identifiable information and that choice will not prevent you from using the GBN Website. Please note, however, if you should choose to withhold requested information, we may not be able to provide you with some of the services dependent upon the collection of this information. 

You can choose at anytime to opt out of receiving emails from GBN or from having your personally identifiable information shared with selected companies. If you want to opt out, you can do so by editing your preferences in your account (profile) in the Website or by writing to us at the addresses mentioned above. If you elect to "opt out" we will not, as applicable, share your personal information with third parties or send you emails. However, we may continue to use your personal information for internal purposes, to enhance your user experience or as necessary to administer the site or comply with applicable law. 

We reserve the right to send a one-time registration confirmation email, notices about new messages, friends, congratulations with birthday, and infrequent Service Alert messages to users to inform them of specific changes that may impact their ability to use a service they have previously signed up for, regardless of email contact opt-in status. We also reserve the right to contact you if compelled to do so as part of a legal proceeding or if there has been a violation of our Terms of Use or applicable licensing agreements. 

Cookies 

Our Website uses "cookie" technology. "Cookies" are short pieces of data generated by a web server that a website stores on a user's computer. Certain pages on our Website may require the use of a cookie for purposes of keeping information you enter on multiple pages together. Cookies also enable us to customize our Website and offerings to your needs and provide you with a better online experience with us. In addition, cookies are used to (i) allow registered users to sign in without typing their sign in name each time; (ii) measure usage of various pages on our Website to help us make our information; more pertinent to your needs and easy for you to access; and (iii) provide functionality such as online orders, GBN's services and other functionality that we believe would be of interest and value to you. 

We do not use cookies to gather information concerning your visits to other websites, nor ascertain any personally identifiable information about you apart from what you voluntarily provide us in your dealings with GBN. Cookies do not, under ordinary circumstances, corrupt or damage your computer, programs, or computer files. 

In addition, the service providers we use to serve and host our advertisements, and/or deliver our emails, use cookies, to track the number of times the Website is accessed and whether the site was accessed from an advertisement. There are no cookies in the advertisement or email. A cookie is placed on your computer only if and when you click on an advertisement or open the email. The cookie generated from the advertisement or email does not contain any personally identifiable information and will remain on your hard drive until you delete it. 

You may set your browser to block cookies (consult the instructions for your particular browser on how to do this), although doing so may adversely affect your ability to perform certain transactions, use certain functionality and access certain content on our Website.
